Gajanan Petnekar

Multitasker, Good Communicator

gajananpetnekar11@gmail.com

07411923433

Belgaum, Karnataka, India



linkedin.com/in/gajanan-petnekar-b75223147

in

Seeking a beginner role to enhance and explore my technical knowledge gained at Gogte University in the last two years and still I want to gain more experience, knowledge make myself on a top position. A hard worker with great attitude and primary goal is to grow individually as well as do my best for the company

EDUCATION

O MCA

Gogte Institute of Technology

08/2018 - 08/2020

6.89

70%

) BCA

Bharatesh College of Computer Applications

07/2015 - 06/2018

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelancing

Worked for Individual Businesses

01/2022 - 06/2022

Belgaum

I have experience in working with individual clients like E-commerce and Personal Businesses.

Task

- I had designed some of websites for my clients and delivered it on time,
- And used manage all sites both front and back end and developed with the help of WordPress,
- And also I have a knowledge on Digital Marketing, where I can handle some of the Ads and SEO.

Industry Management SystemInternship at Omega Soft Solutions

02/2020 - 04/2020

Tasks

Pune

- Industrial management system is computer based system for tracking number of products, finding defective products,
- Measuring the temperature of the products and also we can track the machine status,
- Companies use Industrial management software to avoid less labor work and time.

Lead Exchange

Mini Project

02/2018 - 04/2018

Relaaum

- Tasks
- The Lead Exchange is a transparent, simple and effective platform that enables you to maximize the value of the leads you generate.
- Through a single point of integration you are able to generate many different kinds of leads and sell them in real time to many of potential buyers.

SKILLS



PERSONAL PROJECTS

Result Analyzer

- This is the application which is developed in Android Studio, this applications helps user to check Marks of the particular students
- And it will display Pie chart to display whole report of the class depending scores of particular students

Cafe Booking

- This application is developed using Reactjs and other components, this application helps user to book the table of restaurant
- It uses only Reactjs to work from start to end, used JSON table to fetch data to the front end for the user

CERTIFICATES

Boostrap 4

Hong Kong University of Science & Technology

Angular

Hong Kong University of Science & Technology

React

Hong Kong University of Science & Technology

Machine learning using Python

Ethical Hacking

LANGUAGES

Marathi Native or Bilingual Proficiency English

Full Professional Proficiency

Hindi

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Kannada

Full Professional Proficiency